juiceplus.com 2018-11-18

# Privacy Statement

We appreciate your business, and we value your privacy and security. The Juice Plus+ Company is therefore committed to safeguarding your privacy both online and off, and takes every step possible to ensure that your personal information is secure. Toward that end, we have developed the following comprehensive, global privacy policies.

**We protect your privacy in every way we can think of.**

•    We collect personal information from you only when you choose to provide information to us, such as by purchasing our products.

•    If at any time you wish to review, update, change or delete any information you have provided to us, you may contact your Juice Plus+ representative or contact us directly at [customercare@juiceplus.com](mailto:customercare@juiceplus.com) as set forth under “Contact Information” below.

•    We will only use the personal information you share with us to assist you in conducting business with us.

•    We will not share any of your personal information with any third party, other than business service partners under contract to us who help us serve you better in areas such as fraud prevention, technology services, and specialized customer services. Our contracts dictate that our service partners only use your information in connection with the services they perform for us. Furthermore, in cases where we transfer to third parties personal information of EU and Swiss individuals received pursuant to the EU-US Privacy Shield and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield (see below), respectively, The Juice Plus+ Company, LLC is potentially liable.

•    We may also be required to disclose your personal information in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

•    We may also supplement or combine your personal information with data lawfully obtained from third parties such as banks and credit card processors that assist us in conducting business with you.

•    We will never, under any circumstances whatsoever, sell or rent any of your personal information to any third parties for any purpose, as many other companies do.

•    We may, from time to time, send you e-mails regarding our products. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, simply click on the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the email or contact us as set forth under “Contact Information” below.

•    To assure the high level of personal service for which our company is known, if you choose to become a customer and are not already affiliated with a Juice Plus+ representative, we may assign you a representative and share basic contact information you provide – such as name, phone number, and email address – with them. **This never includes your credit card information or other financial information.**

•    If you choose to become more than a customer, and participate in the Juice Plus+ business, you will need to provide additional personal information to us such as your Social Security and/or Tax ID number. We apply the same safeguards to this additional information as we do to credit card information and other financial information.

•    All Juice Plus+ representatives are also contractually obligated to abide by our privacy and security policies, which include the obligation not to share your personal information with anyone else, under any circumstances.

•    The Juice Plus+ Company is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC).

**We take additional security measures online.**

Keeping your personal financial information private is vitally important to us. Since this can sometimes be a particular problem online, we take these additional security measures in that environment.

•    If you purchase our products online, we need your name, mailing address, and credit card or bank account information in order to fulfill your order. We also request an email address and/or telephone number in order to contact you about your order. Any time we ask for a credit card or bank account number, however, we always transmit that payment information in an encrypted format, which keeps it from being understood by unauthorized people. We use state-of-the-art, industry-standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption to ensure that is the case.

•   If you elect to participate in the Juice Plus+ business, and share Juice Plus+ products with others, we also need your U.S. Social Security number, your Tax ID number, and/or your bank account information in order to compensate you for your efforts on the Company’s behalf.

•    In every case, we take all possible organizational, technical and administrative measures to protect your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, even by a company such as ours that goes to the lengths we do to ensure your privacy and security. In short, we cannot absolutely ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us – no one can – and therefore ultimately you do so at your own risk, though we do everything humanly and technologically possible to minimize that risk.

**Cookies**

If you visit our websites we may save information in the form of “cookies” on your computer or other device.  “Cookies” are text files that are saved on your computer and contain information about you. We use cookies to offer you better service by helping to provide more tailored information to you and to facilitate access to the website and its usage. Cookies also help us keep track of your “shopping cart” before you complete any purchase. We do not allow third parties to place cookies on your computer or other device.

If you wish to turn off the cookies, all major Internet browsers allow you to delete cookies from your computer, to prevent cookies from being saved, or to give a warning before a cookie is saved. However, if you turn off cookies completely, you may not be able to use all of the functions of our websites to their full extent, and some web pages may not display properly.

We may also use web analysis services, either directly or through third party providers, to collect information about your usage of our websites (including your anonymized IP address). We will use this information to evaluate usage of the websites, to create reports about the website activities, and to help us provide further services to our users such as you.

**Statement Updates**

We may update this Privacy Statement from time to time to ensure that it reflects changes in the world around us.  If we do update it, we will always make the updated statement available here for your continued review.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our use of your information or about this Privacy Statement, please contact us at [customercare@juiceplus.com](mailto:customercare@juiceplus.com).

**Special additional statements regarding the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework**

The Juice Plus+ Company complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States, respectively.  The Juice Plus+ Company has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability.  If there is any conflict between the policies in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern.  To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>.

In compliance with the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Principles, The Juice Plus+ Company commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information.  European Union and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact The Juice Plus+ Company via email at [privacy@juiceplus.com](mailto:privacy@juiceplus.com).   

The Juice Plus+ Company has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit [www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/](http://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/) for more information and to file a complaint.

Please note that if your complaint is not resolved through these channels, under limited circumstances, a binding arbitration option may be available before a Privacy Shield Panel.

_Updated and effective April 12, 2017._

Copyright© 2017, The Juice Plus+ Company, LLC, USA. All rights reserved.
